Name
 Zin Moe Htoo

 Date of Birth
 06 / Feb / 1996

 Phone
 +95 9758489854

Address - No(93), Thiri Road, Hlaing Township, Yangon, Myanmar

Email - <u>mhtoo1011@gmail.com</u>
Github - <u>https://github.com/CV-ZMH</u>

LinkedIn - https://www.linkedin.com/in/zin-moe-htoo



Professional Summary

Passionate and self-taught Computer Vision Engineer with 3+ years of industry experience in research and offshore service companies. Excellent problem solving skills, self-initiative and able to work independently with minimal supervision. Able to write efficient, scalable and clean code from POC phase to deployment phase. Highly experienced in the areas of image classification, face recognition, object detection, human pose estimation, image segmentation, object tracking, action recognition and depth estimation.

Technical Skills

Platform : Windows, Unix, Linux Language : Python (proficient)

Frameworks : PyTorch (proficient), Keras, TensorFlow, Fastai, Detectron2

Libraries : Onnx, TensorRT, OpenCV, Scikit-Learn, Numpy, Pandas, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Tensorboard,

Development: Docker, Git, Github, Debugging, Anaconda, Jupyter Notebook, Spyder, Markdown

Deep Learning: Algorithm Implementation, Model Training, Evaluation, Optimization, Hyperparameter Tuning,

Data Augmentation, Exploratory Data Analysis (EDA), Model Ensembling Methods

Experience

Senior Al Engineer, Computer Vision (11/2019 - present)

Global Walkers Co., Ltd.

- Leadership and mentorship to junior Al Engineers through deep learning projects.
- Utilize SOTA models and papers for building and training neural nets to solve problems like object detection, image segmentation, human pose estimation, object tracking, action recognition and depth estimation.
- Develop efficient, scalable baseline code for complex projects like *human action recognition* using skeleton based methods and temporal action localization methods.
- Develop *object detection* projects for real world datasets training and evaluation using YOLOv3-v4-v5, YOLOX, CenterNet, SwinTransformer, Faster RCNN, RetinaNet models.
- Develop semantic segmentation models for real world datasets training and evaluation using SegFormer, Unet, DeepLabv3, HrNet.
- Research and develop *object tracking* models with deepsort, centertrack and FairMOT.
- Design and develop production ready code in python.
- Deploying with Docker and optimizing models using Onnx, TensorRT for Jetson devices.

Al Engineer, Computer Vision (06/2019 - 11/2019)

Metro IT and Japanese Language Center Co., Ltd.

- Responsible for the research, design, and implementation of machine learning and computer vision solutions for real world projects.
- Research and develop face recognition and human motion analysis projects using different background subtraction algorithms, image filters, morphology operations, HOG and SVM.
- Research and develop face recognition and detector based action recognition projects using ResNet, VGG16, YOLOv3, MTCNN, FaceNet.
- Develop people tracking system using centroid tracker with yolov3.

Junior Research & Development Engineer (11/2018 - 5/2019)

ICT Start Group Myanmar Co., Ltd.

- Responsible for researching the latest technologies like IoT and AI trends, and giving presentations of the prototype results to the managers and CEO.
- Develop object detection, face recognition and color tracker prototypes using tensorflow and opency.
- Implement self balancing robot with arduino and raspberry pi.

Education

University of Technology - Yatanarpon Cyber City (11/2012 - 11/2018)

B.E. (ECE) Bachelor of Engineering (Electronics Engineering)

Pyin Oo Lwin, Myanmar

Thesis: Drone with Autonomous Water Spraying System

This thesis was aimed to be helpful and innovative for the agricultural sector in Myanmar. I've built a UAV drone from scratch with APM flight controller. To automate the water spraying system, I've used an image classifier on raspberry pi and trained the model on custom collected plant dataset through google.

Myanmar Institute of Business (MIB) (1/2019 - 5/2019)

ABE Professional Diploma in Artificial Intelligence

Yangon, Myanmar

Project : Agents of Al (AoA)

Our team created a home controlling system with mobile phone using IoT and speech recognition technologies dialogflow api and google assistant.

Certificates and Courses

- Linux Essential Certificate
- Elements of Al Certificate
- Practical Python for Al Coding 2
- Fastai 2019 Course
- ❖ CS231n

Career Objective

To be able to work and grow professionally as Computer Vision Software Engineer in an organization where I could contribute my solid background in programming and deep learning models development for real world applications. My endeavor and dedication in the job will be helpful in achieving the company's goals and objectives.